<area id="jims_house" name="Jim's House">
	<room id="comfy" name="Jim's comfy Room">
		<first_visit>All great stories start in great places. This, however, is a stoy. Not a story. It's a different thing, you see.</first_visit>
		<description>This room is a combination bedroom/computer hole. It smells a bit, but it's comfortable enough.</description>
		<item name="Computer" take="n" container="y">
			<first_visit>You bump your nose on the old monitor.</first_visit>
			<description>Jim's old PC. Mostly used for playing shitty text-based RPGs on his Gentoo system. The side panel is missing</description>
			<altname>PC</altname>
			<altname>comp</altname>
			<item name="Monitor" take="n" part="y">
				<description>It's a CRT and it's grey.</description>
				<altname>screen</altname>
			</item>
			<item name="Inner Workings" take="n">
				<description>You don't know anything about computers! Stop looking at the parts like you know what they're for.</description>
				<ontake>You should be happy it runs Nethack. Leave it be.</ontake>
			</item>
			<item name="Letter" take="y">
				<description>A letter written in an old-fashioned hand. It reads: "jim noooooo, dont be demons jim". The letter is signed.</description>
			</item>
		</item>
	</room>
	<room id="front" name="Foyer">
		<first_visit>A draught comes in from under, above and both sides of the front door. Not surprising considering its condition.</first_visit>
		<description>Calling it a 'foyer' is perhaps talking the room up. This is a vestibule at best.</description>
	</room>
	<room id="kitchen" name="Kitchenette">
		<description>The only thing in this room that offsets the depressing atmosphere is the knowledge that food comes from here.</description>
		<item name="Butane lighter" take="y">
			<description>One of those lighters with a long flexible neck. You bought it so you could actually light the stove.</description>
			<altname>lighter</altname>
		</item>
		<item name="dishes" take="n">
			<description>Neverending.</description>
			<altname>washing up</altname>
		</item>
	</room>
	<exit a="jims_house.comfy" b="jims_house.front" dir="n">
		<description>An open archway. Not a very interesting exit in this case.</description>
	</exit>
	<exit a="jims_house.front" b="jims_house.kitchen" dir="e">
		<description>A small doorway, sans door.</description>
	</exit>
	<exit a="jims_house.front" b="street.garden" dir="w">
		<description>This door is, put plainly, stuffed. After the 'lifting incident', you dare not open it too hard.</description>
		<door default="closed" />
	</exit>
</area>